<?xml version="1.0"?>
<questions>
<date value="2013-11-13">
	<qimage>q1.jpg</qimage>
    <question>Not a single hole in the wall!</question>	
	<answer>rahul dravid</answer>
	<hint>Wazza! Knocked that one out for a six! The location of the next clue is at the finance department in CSRIE<hint/>
	<errors>
		<ehintone>Sorry! But Krishanan PP wants you to try again.</ehintone>
		<ehinttwo>Bowled! Give it another try.</ehinttwo>
		<ehintthree>Nope! Close but not enough! Care to try again? </ehintthree>		
	</errors>
</date>
<date value="2013-11-13">
	<qimage>q2.jpg</qimage>
    <question>Which Indian phone manufacturer is nothing like anything?</question>	
	<answer>micromax</answer>
	<hint>Excellent! You have begun the hunt successfully! The location of the next clue is at library.<hint/>
	<errors>
		<ehintone>Sorry! But Wolverine wants you to try again.</ehintone>
		<ehinttwo>Oops! Give it another try. You know you want to!</ehinttwo>
		<ehintthree>Nope! That was nothing like anything close to the answer :P. Give it another go </ehintthree>		
	</errors>
</date>	
<date value="2013-11-13">	
	<qimage>q3.jpg</qimage>
    <question>The pretty acrobat diva</question>	
	<answer>katrina kaif</answer>
	<hint>MashAllah! Kya bath hai Tiger! The next location is at in front of Krishanan PP's cabin (CSRIE)<hint/>
	<errors>
		<ehintone>Sorry! But Aaliyah wants you to try again.</ehintone>
		<ehinttwo>Wrong move! Get back on that balance rope!</ehinttwo>
		<ehintthree>Nope! She knows you can do it! Again.</ehintthree>		
	</errors>
</date>
<date value="2013-11-13">	
	<qimage>q5.jpg</qimage>
    <question>Next generation battery operated car maker</question>	
	<answer>elon musk</answer>
	<hint>Electrifying! Take the hyperloop to the next clue location which is in the Elevator(CSRIE)!<hint/>
	<errors>
		<ehintone>Sorry! Guess again?</ehintone>
		<ehinttwo>Oops! Give it another try. You know you want to!</ehinttwo>
		<ehintthree>Nope! You dont pay anything to try again pal! </ehintthree>		
	</errors>
</date>	
<date value="2013-11-13">	
	<qimage>q4.jpg</qimage>
    <question>SEO matters</question>	
	<answer>page rank</answer>
	<hint>Simple as googling! The location of the next clue is in front of the HR Dept in CSRIE<hint/>
	<errors>
		<ehintone>Sorry! Have you tried googling it?.</ehintone>
		<ehinttwo>Error! Let's try that again!</ehinttwo>
		<ehintthree>Found no result! Retry with modified answer? </ehintthree>		
	</errors>
</date>
<date value="2013-11-13">	
	<qimage>q6.jpg</qimage>
    <question>Yet another project of Google</question>	
	<answer>project loon</answer>
	<hint>You popped that one! You are so close to the treasure. The last clue is in the Noida Office!!! Just Kidding :P
	The final clue can be found at the Mobility Booth (Booth #1).See you there, 14th Nov 2013, Engage!<hint/>
	<errors>
		<ehintone>Sorry! The answer is blowing in the wind. Try again.</ehintone>
		<ehinttwo>Oops! You didn't hit the hotspot. Refresh search?</ehinttwo>
		<ehintthree>Nope! Make the next one count!</ehintthree>		
	</errors>
</date>		
<date value="2013-11-14">	
	<qimage>q7.jpg</qimage>
    <question>Ask the person on the booth for a hint?</question>	
	<answer>tim berners lee</answer>
	<hint>You Hit GOLD!!!!! Congratulations! Claim your prize at the booth!<hint/>
	<errors>
		<ehintone>Sorry! Imagine if you didn't have the internet to find the answer. </ehintone>
		<ehinttwo>Oops! Give it another try. You know you want to!</ehinttwo>
		<ehintthree>Nope! Skynet needs its. Once more? </ehintthree>		
	</errors>
</date>	
</questions>